simplyglutenfreemag.com 2016-10-19

# Simply Gluten Free Privacy Policy & Guarantee

**Our Guarantee**

Simply Gluten Free Inc. Guarantees all products 100% satisfaction or your money (including shipping) fully returned, without question (except to ask how we can improve ourselves to better serve you and others in the future). Call customer service at (727) 738-5735 or email Julia at [julia@simplygluten-free.com](mailto:julia@simplygluten-free.com)

**Privacy Policy for simplygluten-free.com**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [julia@simplygluten-free.com](mailto:julia@simplygluten-free.com).

At simplygluten-free.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information received and collected by simplygluten-free.com and how it is used.

Like many other websites, simplygluten-free.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movements around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

simplygluten-free.com does use cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the users access or visit, customize web page content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitors send via their browser.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense and Amazon.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to track the advertisements and links that appear on simplygluten-free.com sent directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

simplygluten-free.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

Please consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. simplygluten-free.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you can do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
